A Guide to the Christopher C. Kraft Papers, 1941-1982
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- 1965
  - City of Hampton Award, October-November 1965 (Box-folder 7-9)
  - VPI Distinguished Alumnus Citation, November 11, 1965 (Box-folder 7-10)
  - Audiotape of Convocation for Kraft, november 11, 1965 (Box-folder 7-11)
  - Gemini VI Technical Debriefing, December 20, 1965 (Box-folder 7-12)
  - Gemini VII Technical Debriefing, December 23, 1965 (Box-folder 7-13)
  - GT-4 Flight Crew Debriefing Transcript, c. 1965 (Box-folder 7-14)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1965 (Box-folder 7-15)
  - Cigar Institue of America: Cigar Man of the Year Award, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 7-16)
- 1966
  - Manned Space Flight Experiments Interim Report: Gemini V Mission, January 6, 1966 (Box-folder 7-17)
  - Gemini Program Mission Report: Gemini VI-A, January 1966 (Box-folder 7-18)
  - Gemini Program Missino Report: Gemini VII, Cover through Section 5-102, January 1966 (Box-folder 8-1)
  - Gemini Program Mission Report: Gemini VII, Section 6-1 through End, January 1966 (Box-folder 8-2)
  - Gemini Midprogram Conference, February 23-25, 1966 (Box-folder 8-3)
  - Post-Launch report: Apollo Mission A-004, April 15, 1966 (Box-folder 8-4)
  - Speech to Southern Gas Association: Some Aspects of Manned Space Flight Operations, March 20, 1966 (Box-folder 8-5)
  - Gemini Program Mission Report: Gemini VIII, April 1966 (Box-folder 8-6)
  - Post Launch Report: Mission AS-201, May 6, 1966 (Box-folder 8-7)
  - Honorary Doctorate: Indiana Institute of Technology, May 1966 (Box-folder 8-8)
  - Gemini IXA: Technical Debriefing, June 11, 1966 (Box-folder 8-9)
  - Interim Report: Manned Spaceflight Experiments: Gemini X Mission, July 18-21, 1966 (Box-folder 8-10)
  - Gemini X: Technical Debriefing, June 11, 1966 (Box-folder 8-11)
  - Gemini Program Mission Report: Gemini IX-A, July 1966 (Box-folder 8-12)
  - Gemini X: Gemini Program Mission report, Cover through Section 5-99, August 1966 (Box-folder 9-1)
  - Gemini X: Gemini Program Mission Report, Section 5-100 through Section 7-70, August 1966 (Box-folder 9-2)
  - Gemini X: Gemini Program Mission Report, Section 8-1 through End, August 1966 (Box-folder 9-3)
  - Gemini XI: Technical Debriefing, September 19, 1966 (Box-folder 9-4)
  - Post-Launch Report: Mission AS-202, October 12, 1966 (Box-folder 9-5)
  - Gemini Program Mission Report: Gemini XI, October 1966 (Box-folder 9-6)
  - Manned Space Flight Experiments Interim Report: Gemini IX Mission, November 1, 1966 (Box-folder 9-7)
  - Manned Space Flight Experiments Interim Report: Gemini XII Mission, November 11-15, 1966 (Box-folder 9-8)
  - Presentation at AIAA Meeting: Flight Operations Planning and Preparation for Manned Orbital Missions, November 29-December 2, 1966 (Box-folder 9-9)
  - Apollo News Symposium Presentation, December 15, 1966 (Box-folder 9-10)
  - Christopher Kraft, Jr. Biographical Entry in Current Biography, 1966 (Box-folder 9-11)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1966 (Box-folder 9-12)
  - VPI Correspondence, 1966 (Box-folder 9-13)
- 1967
  - Gemini Program Mission Report: Gemini XII Cover through Section 5-50, January 1967 (Box-folder 9-14)
  - Gemini Program Mission Report: Gemini XII, Section 5-51 through Section 6-44, January 1967 (Box-folder 9-15)
  - Gemini Program Mission Report Gemini XII, Section 7-1 through End, January 1967 (Box-folder 9-16)
  - Rotary Speech, February 1, 1967 (Box-folder 9-17)
  - Apollo 204 Review Board Report: Appendix A, Board Minutes, April 5, 1967 (Box-folder 9-18)
  - Apollo 204 Review Board Report: Appendix B, Witness Statements and Releases, April 5, 1967 (Box-folder 9-19)
  - Apollo 204 Review Board Report: Appendix C Section 1, Apollo Operations Handbook, April 5, 1967 (Box-folder 9-20)
  - Apollo 204 Review Board Report: Appendic C Section 2, Apollo Operations Handbook Continued, April 5, 1967 (Box-folder 9-21)
  - Apollo 204 Review Board Report: Appendix D Panels 1-4, April 5, 1967 (Box-folder 10-1)
  - Apollo 204 Review Board Report: Appendix D Panel 5, April 5, 1967 (Box-folder 10-2)
  - Apollo 204 Review Board Report: Appendix D Panels 6-10, April 5, 1967 (Box-folder 10-3)
  - Apollo 204 Review Board report: Appendix D Panels 12-17, April 5, 1967 (Box-folder 10-43)
  - Apollo 204 Review Board report: Apendix D panel 18, April 5, 1967 (Box-folder 10-5)
  - Apollo 204 review Board Report: Appendix D Panels 19-21, April 5, 1967 (Box-folder 10-6)
  - Apollo 204 Review Board Report: Appendix E, April 5, 1967 (Box-folder 10-7)
  - Apollo 204 Review Board Report: Appendix F and Appendix G, April 5, 1967 (Box-folder 10-8)
  - Gemini TCA Anomalies Investigation, April 28, 1967 (Box-folder 10-9)
  - Duke University Speech: The Significance of Our Space Program, May 9, 1967 (Box-folder 10-10)
  - Virginia Press Association Award, June 1967 (Box-folder 10-11)
  - Summary of Gemini Extravehicular Activity, June 1967 (Box-folder 10-12)
  - Tape Transcription, June 19, 1967 (Box-folder 10-13)
  - Presentation: Science and Technology Advisory Committee, July 8, 1967 (Box-folder 10-14)
  - Speech to Cape Canaveral Press Club: Progress in FLight Operations Development, July 18, 1967 (Box-folder 10-15)
  - ASME Spirit of St. Louis Award, July 1967 (Box-folder 10-16)
  - Honorary Degree: Parks College of Aeronautical Technology, St. Louis University, July 28,1967 (Box-folder 10-17)
  - Speech: Mis-Continent Oil and Gas Association, September 12, 1967 (Box-folder 10-18)
  - Goddard Engineering Lecture Series, September 12, 1967 (Box-folder 10-19)
  - Transcript of Interview, October 5, 1967 (Box-folder 10-20)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1967 (Box-folder 10-21)
  - Summary Report: Apollo 204 Fire-Related Changes, 1967 (Box-folder 10-22)
  - Article for Yale Newspaper, c.1967 (Box-folder 10-23)
- 1968
  - Apollo 4 Mission Report, January 1968 (Box-folder 10-24)
  - Speech: Texas Safety Association, March 19, 1968 (Box-folder 10-25)
  - Apollo 5 Mission Report, Cover through Section 6.9-1, March 1968 (Box-folder 10-26)
  - Apollo 5 Mission Report, Section 6.10-1 through End, March 1968 (Box-folder 10-27)
  - Speech to Greensboro College, April 18-19, 1968 (Box-folder 10-28)
  - Speech to Dedicate Cullen College of Engineering Building at University of Houston, May 3, 1968 (Box-folder 10-29)
  - Apollo 6 Mission Report, Cover through Section 5.14-25, May 1968 (Box-folder 10-30)
  - Apollo 6 Mission Report, Section 5.14-26 through End, May 1968 (Box-folder 10-31)
  - Presentation to Aerospace Safety Advisory Panel on Flight Mission Rules, June 12, 1968 (Box-folder 11-1)
  - Apollo 7 Technical Debriefing: Part 1, October 27, 1968 (Box-folder 11-2)
  - Appolo 7 Technical Debriefing: Part 2, October 27, 1968 (Box-folder 11-3)
  - Apollo 7 Mission Report, December 1968 (Box-folder 11-4)
  - Presentation to Boeing/Michoud Employees on Flight Systems Quality in Manned Space Flight, December 11, 1968 (Box-folder 11-5)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1968 (Box-folder 11-6)
  - Virginia Tech Correspondence, 1968 (Box-folder 11-7)
- 1969
  - Apollo 8 Technical Debriefing, January 2, 1969 (Box-folder 11-8)
  - Presentation to the National Wholesale Furniture Association on Apollo 8 Mission to the Moon, January 8, 1969 (Box-folder 11-9)
  - Virginians of Maryland Medallions of Honor Award, January 25, 1969 (Box-folder 11-10)
  - Apollo Mission Operation Report: Supplement, February 25, 1969 (Box-folder 11-12)
  - Apollo Mission Report, February, 1969 (Box-folder 11-12)
  - Apollo 9 Mission: AS-504, February 1969 (Box-folder 11-13)
  - Bell Aerosystems Report: Lunar Landing Training Vehicle (Vehiclle No.1) Flight Test Summary Report, March 12, 1969 (Box-folder 11-14)
  - Apollo 11: Documents and Memoranda, March-April, 1969 (Box-folder 11-15)
  - Mission Operations Working Group, March 25, 1969 (Box-folder 11-16)
  - Lunar Landing Training Vehicle (LLTR No.2), March-May 1969 (Box-folder 11-17)
  - Apollo 11: DCR Agenda and Exhibits, April 8, 1969 (Box-folder 11-18)
  - Manned Space Flight Council meeting, April 8-9, 1969 (Box-folder 11-19)
  - Configuration Control Board Meeting, April 10, 1969 (Box-folder 11-20)
  - Press Briefing on Apollo Program, April 14, 1969 (Box-folder 11-21)
  - Post-Apollo Program Definition: NASA Management Council, April 1969 (Box-folder 11-22)
  - Apollo Article for The New York Times, April-June, 1969 (Box-folder 11-23)
  - Apollo 9 Mission Report, May 9, 1969 (Box-folder 11-24)
  - Presentation: Northeast electronics Research and engineering Meeting, May 1969 (Box-folder 11-25)
  - Apollo 10 Technical Crew Debriefing, June 2, 1969 (Box-folder 11-26)
  - Presentation to Operations Management Group, June 18, 1969 (Box-folder 11-27)
  - Apollo 11 AS-506 Mission, June 24, 1969 (Box-folder 11-28)
  - Interview with Kraft, June 1969 (Box-folder 11-29)
  - Apollo Lunar Exploration Missions: CSM Modifications, July 7, 1969 (Box-folder 12-1)
  - NASA/GAEC LMMP Configuration Control Board, July 7, 1969 (Box-folder 12-2)
  - Mexican Television Guide with Feature on Neil Armstrong and Apollo 11, July 22, 1969 (Box-folder 12-3)
  - Apollo 11 Letters of Appreciation, July 29-30, 2969 (Box-folder 12-4)
  - Shuttle Project: Notes and Report, July 30, 1969 (Box-folder 12-5)
  - Apollo 11 Technical Crew Debriefing, July 31, 1969 (Box-folder 12-6)
  - Apollo 11 EVA: Miscellaneous Documents, July 1969 (Box-folder 12-7)
  - Mission Operation Report: Apollo Supplement, July 1969 (Box-folder 12-8)
  - Apollo 10 Mission Report, August 1969 (Box-folder 12-9)
  - Notes on Apollo 11 Extended Mission, August 1969 (Box-folder 12-10)
  - Gilruth Interview, August 26, 1969 (Box-folder 12-11)
  - Apollo Lunar Exploration Mission Review, September 5, 1969 (Box-folder 12-12)
  - Lunar Samples from Apollo 11, September 5, 1969 (Box-folder 12-13)
  - Reference Materials for Demonstration of Lunar Surveying System, Roving Vehicles, and Data Facility Operations, September 29-30, 1969 (Box-folder 12-14)
  - Report for the Space Task Group, September 1969 (Box-folder 12-15)
  - AIAA Annual Meeting, October 20-24, 1969 (Box-folder 12-16)
  - Apollo 13 Landing Site: Fra Mauro, October 1969 (Box-folder 12-17)
  - Apollo 11 Mission Report, November 1969 (Box-folder 12-18)
  - Aeromedical Directorate Status Review, November 26, 1969 (Box-folder 12-19)
  - Apollo 12 Technical Crew Debriefing, December 1, 1969 (Box-folder 12-20)
  - Photo of Apollo 12 EVA 2 Traverse, December 1969 (Box-folder 12-21)
  - George Low Interviews, 1969 (Box-folder 12-22)
  - Apollo Project Memoranda, 1969 (Box-folder 12-23)
  - Apollo Project Memoranda, Documents, etc., 1969 (Box-folder 12-24)
  - Post-Apollo Mission Definition and Status Report, 1969 (Box-folder 12-25)
  - Articles on Mercury, Gemini, and Apollo Flights from 'Aerospace Medicicne,' 1969-1970 (Box-folder 12-27)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1969 (Box-folder 12-26)
- 1970
  - Space Shuttle Overview: McDonnell Douglas Corp., January 2, 1970 (Box-folder 13-1)
  - Interview with Kraft and C. Donlan, January 15, 1970 (Box-folder 13-2)
  - Speech to University Club, New York, January 17, 1970 (Box-folder 13-3)
  - Personal Notes, January-June, 1970 (Box-folder 13-4)
  - Shuttle Program, Phase B Study Program Review, January 1970 (Box-folder 13-5)
  - NASA FY 1971 Budget Briefing, February 2, 1970 (Box-folder 13-6)
  - Manned Space Flight Studies: First Quarterly Review, February 11, 1970 (Box-folder 13-7)
  - Space Shuttle Program: Phase B Definition, March 13, 1970 (Box-folder 13-8)
  - Review of Langley Space Shuttle Activity, March 2, 1970 (Box-folder 13-9)
  - Space Station Program: Phase B Definition, March 13, 1970 (Box-folder 13-10)
  - Preliminary Findings of the Lightning Incident During the Apollo 12 Launch, 1970 (Box-folder 13-11)
  - Apollo 12 Mission Report, March 1970 (Box-folder 13-12)
  - Article in Astronautics and Aeronautics: Flexible Yet Disciplined Mission Planning, March 1970 (Box-folder 13-13)
  - Space Station Second Quarterly Review, March 1970 (Box-folder 13-14)
  - Honorary Membership: Aerospace Medical Association, March-April, 1970 (Box-folder 13-15)
  - VPI Visiting Scholar Program: Speech, April 23-24, 1970 (Box-folder 13-16)
  - Apollo 13 Technical Crew Debriefing, April 24, 1970 (Box-folder 13-17)
  - DC-3 Space Shuttle Study, Vol I, April 27, 1970 (Box-folder 13-18)
  - DC-3 Space Shuttle Study, Vol. II, April 27, 1970 (Box-folder 13-19)
  - Lunar Landing Site Summary Book, April 1970 (Box-folder 13-20)
  - Proceedings: NASA Conference on Materials for Improved Fire Safety, May 6-7, 1970 (Box-folder 13-21)
  - Speech: Aviation/Space Writers Association, May 21, 1970 (Box-folder 13-22)
  - AAS Spaceflight Award, May-June 1970 (Box-folder 13-23)
  - Report: Apollo 13 Review Board, June 15, 1970 (Box-folder 13-24)
  - Report Apollo 13 Review Board - Appendix A, June 15, 1970 (Box-folder 13-25)
  - Report: Apollo 13 Review Board - Appendices B,C,D and E, June 15, 1970 (Box-folder 13-26)
  - Report: Apollo 13 Review Board - Appendices F, G, and H, June 15, 1970 (Box-folder 13-27)
  - Space Station Program: Phase B Definition, Third Quearterly Progress Report, June 19, 1970 (Box-folder 13-28)
  - Space Shuttle System: Statement of Work, Program Definition - Phase B, June 1970 (Box-folder 13-29)
  - Flight Control Division: Advanced Technology Brief Notebook, July 17, 1970 (Box-folder 14-1)
  - Press Kit: Apollo 11 Anniversary, July 20, 1970 (Box-folder 14-2)
  - Goodyear Aerospace Co.: Geologic Exploration with High-Resolution Radar, July 1970 (Box-folder 14-3)
  - Personal Notes, July-December 1970 (Box-folder 14-4)
  - Photo Album: Apollo Cryogenic Gas Storage System Progress Review, August 7, 1970 (Box-folder 14-5)
  - John Commonsense Design Criteria Manual Memorandum: FCD Task A-15, August 6, 1970 (Box-folder 14-6)
  - Alternate Shuttle Concepts Study, August 1970 (Box-folder 14-7)
  - New Apollo Oxygen Tank Design, August 1970 (Box-folder 14-8)
  - Presentation to Space Station Utilization Conference: Space Station Operations, September 9, 1970 (Box-folder 14-9)
  - Space Shuttle: Critical Decisions Briefing, September 15, 1970 (Box-folder 14-10)
  - Tidal Gravimeter, September 18, 1970 (Box-folder 14-11)
  - Review of Shuttle Status and Issues, September 18, 1970 (Box-folder 14-12)
  - Space Shuttle Traffic Model: Notes, September 18, 1970 (Box-folder 14-13)
  - Apollo 13 Mission Report, September 1970 (Box-folder 14-14)
  - Extravehicular-Activity Experience in Manned Space Operations, September 1970 (Box-folder 14-15)
  - Space Shuttle Orbiter Selection Review, October 1, 1970 (Box-folder 14-16)
  - Space Shuttle Phase B 90-Day Review and Special Interest Topics Briefing, October 13, 1970 (Box-folder 14-17)
  - Skylab Preliminary Reference Trajectory, October 13, 1970 (Box-folder 14-18)
  - Engineering Memorandum: Study of Materials Selection for Space Shuttle Orbiter Structure and TPS, October 20, 1970 (Box-folder 14-19)
  - AIAA Fellows Dinner, October 21, 1970 (Box-folder 14-20)
  - Louis W. Hill Space Transportation Award, October 22, 1970 (Box-folder 14-21)
  - Major Test Facilies of the Engineering and Development Directorate, October 1970 (Box-folder 14-22)
  - Space Shuttle Launch Operations Study: First Interim Report, November 4, 1970 (Box-folder 14-23)
  - Launch Window Scans and Associated Mission Planning Data for 1972, November 12, 1970 (Box-folder 14-24)
  - Space Shuttle Study: Erection, Mating, and Transporting, November 15, 1970 (Box-folder 14-25)
  - Earth Resources Aircraft Project: Aircraft and Sensors, November 1970 (Box-folder 14-26)
  - Speech: Colorado Motor Carriers Association, December 3, 1970 (Box-folder 14-27)
  - USSR/US Docking Study Review, December 21, 1970 (Box-folder 14-28)
  - Five Month Review: Alternate Space Shuttle Concepts Study, December 1970 (Box-folder 14-29)
  - Grumann/Boeing Study: Interim SIC, December 1970 (Box-folder 14-30)
  - Apollo 12 Photographs, 1970 (Box-folder 15-1)
  - George Low Interviews, 1970 (Box-folder 15-2)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1970 (Box-folder 15-3)
  - Photograph of Lunar Surface Sample, 1970 (Box-folder 15-4)
  - Report of the Committee on Science and Astronautics: For the Benefit of All Mankind, A Survey of the Practical Returns from Space Investment, September 14, 1970 (Box-folder 15-5)
  - Reference Material for Speeches, 1970 (Box-folder 15-6)
  - Role of the Shuttle in the National Space Program: Shuttle Notes and Documents, 1970 (Box-folder 15-7)
  - The Shuttle: Its Meaning to the Nation and Florida, 1970 (Box-folder 15-8)
  - The Shuttle: Its Meaning to the Nation and California, 1970 (Box-folder 15-9)
  - Space Shuttle: Legislative and Executive Cotntact Plan, 1970 (Box-folder 15-10)
  - Virginia Tech Correspondence, 1970 (Box-folder 15-11)
- 1971
  - Space Shuttle: Phase B, 180 Day Review Summary, January 13, 1971 (Box-folder 15-12)
  - Space Shuttle Flying Qualities, January 20-21, 1971 (Box-folder 15-13)
  - Space Shuttle: Baseline Descriptions, Vol. I, January 25, 1971 (Box-folder 15-14)
  - Space Shuttle: Baseline Descriptions, Vol.II, January 25, 1971 (Box-folder 15-15)
  - Personal Notes, January 1971 (Box-folder 15-16)
  - Terrain Photography from Gemini Spacecraft: Final Geologic Report, January 1971 (Box-folder 15-17)
  - NCAA Theodore Roosevelt Award, January 1971 (Box-folder 15-18)
  - The Shuttle Program: Its Economic Impact on California, February 8, 1971 (Box-folder 15-19)
  - Earth Observation Program at MSC: Proposed Plan, February 9, 1971 (Box-folder 15-20)
  - Apollo 14 Technical Crew Debriefing, February 17, 1971 (Box-folder 15-21)
  - Apollo 14 Post-Launch Mission Operation Report No. 1, February 22, 1971 (Box-folder 15-22)
  - Post-Skylab Missions Study, February 24, 1971 (Box-folder 15-23)
  - Personal Notes, February 1971 (Box-folder 15-24)
  - Summary Paper: Space Program Benefits, Febraury 1971 (Box-folder 15-25)
  - Shuttle Alternate Concepts Study: 8 Month Review, March 12, 1971 (Box-folder 15-26)
  - Speech: Space Shuttle Development, Testing, and Operations, March 15, 1971 (Box-folder 15-27)
  - IBM Participation in Phase B Shuttle Definition, March 19, 1971 (Box-folder 15-28)
  - External H2 Tank Orbiter Heat-Sink Booster, March 25, 1971 (Box-folder 15-29)
  - Twentieth Texas Conferance, March 26-28, 1971 (Box-folder 15-30)
  - AIAA Louis W. Hill Space Transportation Award, March 1971 (Box-folder 15-31)
  - Personal Notes, March 1971 (Box-folder 15-32)
  - Skylab A: EREP Users Handbook, March 1971 (Box-folder 16-1)
  - Space Shuttle: The Next Logical Step, March 1971 (Box-folder 16-2)
  - Shuttle Phase B, 270 Day Review and Special Interest Topics, April 22, 1971 (Box-folder 16-3)
  - Shuttle Program Review 270 Day Status and Selected Issues, April 22, 1971 (Box-folder 16-4)
  - Aerospace Medical Association Speech, April 26, 1971 (Box-folder 16-5)
  - Alt. Shuttle contract: External H2 Tank Orbiter Heat Sink Booster, 10th Month, April 28, 1971 (Box-folder 16-6)
  - Post Skylab Mission Review, April 29, 1971 (Box-folder 16-7)
  - Personal Notes, April 1971 (Box-folder 16-8)
  - Orbital External H2 Tank Study, Mid-Term Review May 12, 1971 (Box-folder 16-9)
  - Apollo 14 Mission Report, May 1971 (Box-folder 16-10)
  - Drone Aircraft Operational Experience (Jet Transport All-Weather Landing), May 1971 (Box-folder 16-11)
  - Personal Notes, May 1971 (Box-folder 16-12)
  - Speech - Chicago Gynecological Society, June 18, 1971 (Box-folder 16-13)
  - Personal Notes, June 1971 (Box-folder 16-14)
  - On the Moon With Apollo 15, June 1971 (Box-folder 16-15)
  - Boeing/Seattle Notes and Graphics (Shuttle Boosters), 1971 (Box-folder 16-16)
  - Personal Notes, July 1971 (Box-folder 16-17)
  - Apollo 15 Technical Crew Debriefing, August 14, 1971 (Box-folder 16-18)
  - Reusable S-1C Block I-Block II Program, August 20, 1971 (Box-folder 16-19)
  - Eval. Of S-1C/ Cradle As Interim Booster, August 1971 (Box-folder 16-20)
  - Personal Notes, August 1971 (Box-folder 16-21)
  - Alt Shuttle Concepts Study/ Interim Review, September 1, 1971 (Box-folder 16-22)
  - Shuttle Phase B Extension, Mid-Tem review, September 1, 1971 (Box-folder 16-23)
  - Shuttle: OMSF Mid-Term Review, September 1, 1971 (Box-folder 16-24)
  - Alt. Shuttle Contract Study/ Design Requirements Phased Progress Evaluation, September 1, 1971 (Box-folder 16-25)
  - Phase B Shuttle Systems Study/ Interim Report to OMSF, September 1, 1971 (Box-folder 16-26)
  - Board of Directors, Presbyterian Hospital, NM,September 10, 1971 (Box-folder 16-27)
  - Personal Notes, September 1971 (Box-folder 16-28)
  - Space Rescue Considerations, September 20-24, 1971 (Box-folder 16-29)
  - Shuttle Avionics Phase B Extension Mid-Term Review, October 8, 1971 (Box-folder 16-30)
  - Personal Notes, October 1971 (Box-folder 16-31)
  - VPI - Alumni Institute Visit to MSC, November 12, 1971 (Box-folder 16-32)
  - Plan for the Remote Sensing/ Compliance Determniation System for ASCS (soil conserv.), November 15, 1971 (Box-folder 16-33)
  - Speech - Sports Celebrity Dinner, St. Louis, MI, November 18,1971 (Box-folder 16-34)
  - Speech - Blue Ridge Section and Student Group, AIAA, November 19,1971 (Box-folder 16-35)
  - MSC Earth Observation Program Review, November 1971 (Box-folder 16-36)
  - Personal Notes, November 1971 (Box-folder 16-37)
  - Apollo 15 - Mission Report, December 1971 (Box-folder 16-38)
  - Personal Notes, December 1971 (Box-folder 16-39)
  - Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation SVC (ASCS) Presentation RE Aerial Monitoring, 1971 (Box-folder 17-1)
  - Apollo 14 Photographs, 1971 (Box-folder 17-2)
  - Flight Crew Training Aids Etc., 1971 (Box-folder 17-3)
  - Logicon, Inc., Annual Report, 1971 (Box-folder 17-4)
  - Lunar Module EVA Return Chart, 1971 (Box-folder 17-5)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1971 (Box-folder 17-6)
  - Speech Reference Material, 1971 (Box-folder 17-7)
  - Space Shuttle Applications Planning Committee Organizational Chart, 1971 (Box-folder 17-8)
  - Unidentified Aerial (IR) Photos, 1971 (Box-folder 17-9)
  - USSR Report on Luna 16, 1971 (Box-folder 17-10)
  - Virginia Tech Correspondence, 1971 (Box-folder 17-11)
  - S-192 Multispectral Scanner Review, January 31, 1971 (Box-folder 17-12)
  - National VFW Space Award, September 1971 (Box-folder 17-31)
- 1972
  - Personal Notes, January 1972 (Box-folder 17-13)
  - Personal Notes, February 1972 (Box-folder 17-14)
  - Personal Notes, March 1972 (Box-folder 17-15)
  - On the Moon with Apollo 16, April 1972 (Box-folder 17-16)
  - The "Advocates" Show, April 1972 (Box-folder 17-17)
  - Personal Notes, April 1972 (Box-folder 17-18)
  - Apollo 16 Technical Crew Debriefing, May 5, 1972 (Box-folder 17-19)
  - National Association of Credit Management, May 22, 1972 (Box-folder 17-20)
  - Personal Notes, May 1972 (Box-folder 17-21)
  - Colorado College Lecture, 1972 (Box-folder 17-22)
  - Men of Science Award, June 1972 (Box-folder 17-23)
  - Personal Notes, June 1972 (Box-folder 17-24)
  - Kraft Interview by Robert Sherrod, July 27, 1972 (Box-folder 17-25)
  - Personal Notes, July 1972 (Box-folder 17-26)
  - Apollo 16 Mission Report, August 1972 (Box-folder 17-27)
  - Personal Notes, August 1972 (Box-folder 17-28)
  - Houston Baptist College Speech, September 28, 1972 (Box-folder 17-29)
  - Personal Notes, September 1972 (Box-folder 17-30)
  - Concordia College, October 12, 1972 (Box-folder 17-32)
  - Personal Notes, October 1972 (Box-folder 17-33)
  - Gilruth Interview by Robert Sherrod, November 16, 1972 (Box-folder 17-34)
  - Personal Notes, November 1972 (Box-folder 17-35)
  - Kraft Interview by Henry Still, December 16, 1972 (Box-folder 17-36)
  - On the Moon with Apollo 17, December 1972 (Box-folder 17-37)
  - Personal Notes, December 1972 (Box-folder 17-38)
  - George Low Interview with Robert Sherrod, 1972 (Box-folder 17-39)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1972 (Box-folder 17-40)
  - Reference Material for CCK Speeches 1972 (Box-folder 17-41)